{
  "name": "Paper Mario 64",
  "author": "Nameless",
  "is_default": true,
  "tags": ["paper mario", "nintendo 64", "n64", "64", "pm", "mario", "nintendo"],
  "qas":[
	{
		"id": 0,
		"question": "For what system is Paper Mario 64 made?",
		"answer": ["n64", "nin64", "nintendo 64", "64"],
		"points": 1
	},
	{
		"id": 1,
		"question": "Who is the first partner you get?",
		"answer": ["goombario"],
		"points": 1
	},
		{
		"id": 2,
		"question": "What's the name of Goombario's younger sister? ",
		"answer": ["goombaria"],
		"points": 1
	},
	{
		"id": 3,
		"question": "What is the color of the block you can break with the first Hammer you got?",
		"answer": ["yellow"],
		"points": 1
	},
	{
		"id": 4,
		"question": "What ability does Goombario frequently use? (The one that costs 1fp)",
		"answer": ["tattle", "snitch"],
		"points": 1
	},
	{
		"id": 5,
		"question": "That color pants was the Goomba King wearing? Red and: ",
		"answer": ["white"],
		"points": 1
	},
	{
		"id": 6,
		"question": "Which of Mario's battle commands is on the far left side? (top most one)",
		"answer": ["strategies", "flag", "the flag"],
		"points": 2
	},
	{
		"id": 7,
		"question": "How many windows does the Goomba House in Goomba Village have?",
		"answer": ["1", "one"],
		"points": 2
	},
	{
		"id": 8,
		"question": "What is the name of the leader of the Red and Blue Goomba Bros.? ",
		"answer": ["goomba king", "the goomba king"],
		"points": 2
	},
	{
		"id": 9,
		"question": "What color are Luigi's pants? ",
		"answer": ["blue"],
		"points": 1
	},
	{
		"id": 10,
		"question": "How many members are there in Goombario's family?",
		"answer": ["6", "six"],
		"points": 2
	},
	{
		"id": 11,
		"question": "What do you receive when you answer one of Chuck Quizmo's quizes correctly?",
		"answer": ["star piece", "a star piece", "star pieces"],
		"points": 1
	},
	{
		"id": 12,
		"question": "What is the name of the smart Toad living in Toad Town, the one you give the dictionary to? ",
		"answer": ["russ", "russ t", "russ t."],
		"points": 3
	},
	{
		"id": 13,
		"question": "How many buildings are there in Koopa Village? ",
		"answer": ["6", "six"],
		"points": 2
	},
	{
		"id": 14,
		"question": "The members of the Koopa Bros. are Red, Yellow, Green, and: ",
		"answer": ["black"],
		"points": 2
	},	
	{
		"id": 15,
		"question": " How many coins are needed to buy a Mushroom at the shop in Koopa Village? ",
		"answer": ["4", "four", "4 coins", "four coins"],
		"points": 2
	},
	{
		"id": 16,
		"question": "Where does Merluvlee, who tells fortunes, live? ",
		"answer": ["shooting star summit"],
		"points": 3
	},	
	{
		"id": 17,
		"question": "What is the name of the character who joined you at the Koopa Bros. Fortress?",
		"answer": ["bombette"],
		"points": 1
	},	
	{
		"id": 18,
		"question": "What is the color of Bowser's hair? ",
		"answer": ["red"],
		"points": 1
	},	
	{
		"id": 19,
		"question": "How many Star Spirits do you have to save?",
		"answer": ["7", "seven"],
		"points": 1
	},	
	{
		"id": 20,
		"question": "What is the name of the elderly Koopa Troopa who always asks for errands to be run? ",
		"answer": ["koopa koot", "koot"],
		"points": 3
	},
	{
		"id": 21,
		"question": "How many Bob-ombs besides Bombette were imprisioned in the jail at the Koopa Bros. Fortress? ",
		"answer": ["4", "four"],
		"points": 2
	},
	{
		"id": 22,
		"question": "Where is the house of the explorer, Kolorado? ",
		"answer": ["koopa village"],
		"points": 2
	},
	{
		"id": 23,
		"question": "What is the destination of the train that departs from Toad Town Station? ",
		"answer": ["mt rugged", "mt. rugged", "mount rugged", "rugged mountain"],
		"points": 3
	},
	{
		"id": 24,
		"question": "What is the name of the fellow who sells Badges in Toad Town?",
		"answer": ["rowf"],
		"points": 3
	},
	{
		"id": 25,
		"question": "What treasure did Bowser steal from Star Haven?",
		"answer": ["star rod", "the star rod"],
		"points": 1
	},
	{
		"id": 26,
		"question": "What is the color of the roof of the house in Koopa Village where you can listen to the radio? ",
		"answer": ["blue"],
		"points": 3
	},
	{
		"id": 27,
		"question": "Who does Kooper idolize?",
		"answer": ["kolorado", "professor kolorado", "prof. kolorado", "prof kolorado"],
		"points": 2
	},
	{
		"id": 28,
		"question": "What enemy hides inside a coffin in Dry Dry Ruins?",
		"answer": ["poison pokey", "pokey"],
		"points": 2
	},
	{
		"id": 29,
		"question": "What kind of item can you get when you take Star Pieces to Merlow at Shooting Star Summit?",
		"answer": ["badge", "badges"],
		"points": 2
	},
	{
		"id": 30,
		"question": "Who knew the location of the Dry Dry Ruins in the Dry Dry Desert? ",
		"answer": ["moustafa"],
		"points": 3
	},
	{
		"id": 31,
		"question": "To make Lemon Candy, what do you need besides a lemon?",
		"answer": ["cake mix"],
		"points": 3
	},
	{
		"id": 32,
		"question": "What is the name of the item that drops when you hit a whacka on Mt. Rugged?",
		"answer": ["whacka's bump", "whackas bump", "whacka bump"],
		"points": 3
	},
	{
		"id": 33,
		"question": "Other than Lemons, what fruit drops when you hit a tree in the desert oasis? ",
		"answer": ["lime", "limes"],
		"points": 3
	},
	{
		"id": 34,
		"question": "What is Bombette's specialty attack (the one that costs 3fp)",
		"answer": ["bomb"],
		"points": 2
	}
	
  ]
}